Hey world, it's me, and today I'm getting ready to go to the Academy Museum Gala.
Come along as we all collectively glam it up.
Let's do it.
It's like
skin, hair is getting set, set exactly.
We're gonna do a brown eye, brown nails, the dress is brown, my hair is a form of brown,
so I kind of just want to do a monochromatic look tonight.
Oski!
I hear you.
Stop it.
Oscar, you put a sweater on?
Oh, you're so cute.
Oski has a sister.
I'll bring her up here after.
Her name's Piggy.
Piggy will make an appearance.
She's really cute.
Because the dress is like this really pretty dark brown, and I kind of want to do a little bit lighter of a color on the nails.
That looks nice.
Something that I do really like for fall is like monochromatic fall colors.
So like berry colors in makeup, browns, tans, beiges.
I think that I get very inspired by the seasons.
We're going to try this kind of like little flipped blowout.
And we're going to see how it looks, and if we hate it, then we'll have to quickly pivot.
Exactly.
It's going to be like voluminous 90s blowout.
But with a flip.
With a little flip on the ends.
I do feel like I wear my hair up often.
So I feel like, I don't know.
I just wanted to switch it up today.
I think it feeds a little bit more into the monochromatic look that I wanna go for with the dress and the makeup and the hair.
Obviously, I had to do my peptide glazing fluid and barrier restore cream, which is how I always prep my skin for any makeup or any
carpet.
Well, the first thing that always is the plan is the outfit, because you can really decide what what you want to do with your hair and makeup
until you know what you're going to wear.
So we tried the dress on on Thursday.
Today is Saturday.
So once we decided, I think I started thinking about what I might want the vibe to be for the hair and makeup, and
then, you know, we usually set aside at least two, two and a half hours to get ready, figure it out, get everything done.
Kind of all collectively came to a decision.
We're almost there.
As soon as I'm done with these nails, it's time to get dressed, and then we're really almost there.
Home straight, a snack.
I just ordered some soup.
Soup girl loves soup.
This is the dress, putting on the shoes.
So this is YSL, and they made this really beautiful custom brown color for me.
Which I'm very grateful for because I love it.
Put this in the gown.
So the jewelry is Tiffany's.
And we just have some really pretty gemstones.
That from the archive, from the safe.
Not for sale.
I'm not doing anything too crazy with the jewelry, just because I feel like the dress is simple, and I want everything to feel kind of simple still.
This is Piggy.
This is Oscar's little sister.
She's very small.
She's a really sweet little girl.
Say hello, Piggy.
Piggy Lou Bieber, everyone.
Guys, we have to make the final decision, game day decision right now.
Do we like this?
I mean, I love the hair down, too.
Carla?
I'm coming.
Okay.
I'm making a decision.
I can't decide.
I'm usually like.
I feel like it's usually obvious.
I know, I'm usually like.
Yeah.
That's also.
It's down.
I think so, too.
Now that you just did that.
And also, did you just say anything?
And then it fell a little bit forward.
It's very nice.
I love that.
This is it.
I'm about to walk out the door.
Very excited.
And I love my look.
Almost decided to change the hair last minute, but we didn't.
So here it goes.
See you next time.